Sir, result review also, which stock
ICICI LBA futures should I review.  The
results can be said to be slightly below expectations.
But the internals of the results are
very strong.  Ah, the retail health segment
's growth of over 60%
seems to be appealing to the market.  In almost
all the brokerage reports that I have received, the
targets have been seen increasing.
So in that sense, I think the numbers are
okay.  There is no such thing as a problem.
But if for some reason there is an
opportunity to buy near the open support level below.  There
is strong support at 1805.  It will appear to strengthen further above 1915.
JP Morgan has increased the target
from 1940 to 2170.  Goldman has targeted 1925 to
1965.  The target of Makri is
only 2350, so good reports have come.  ICC
Lomar